{
    "id": "7240d61c55e94ed3bc35aad889a90c65",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "To take someone under your wing is to ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hide them",
                "take care of them",
                "suffocate them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To eat the humble pie is to  ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "eat very little",
                "eat greedily",
                "make a humble apology"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "To get out of the bed on the wrong side is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "injure yourself",
                "defeat yourself",
                "be in a particularly irritable mood"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "To make the feathers fly is to ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cause turmoil",
                "establish peace",
                "make a lot of noise"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What does itsy-bitsy mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "magnificent",
                "tiny",
                "soft"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To dilly-dally is to …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have a good time",
                "waste time",
                "make good use of time"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I still miss the ……………………. of university life.",
            "description": "Hurly-burly means busy activity.",
            "answers": [
                "willy-nilly",
                "wishy-washy",
                "hurly-burly"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "To live in straitened circumstances is to live in ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "opulence",
                "poverty",
                "pain"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the expression wishy-washy mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weak",
                "strong",
                "efficient"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to cooperate ………………………",
            "description": "Willy-nilly means whether you like it or not. ",
            "answers": [
                "willy-nilly",
                "dilly-dally",
                "itsy-bitsy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "To be at loggerheads is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "approve",
                "agree",
                "disagree strongly"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Bete noire means an object of ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "affection",
                "admiration",
                "aversion"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}